<StructuredTextModel xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/Omron.Cxap.Modules.StructuredText.Core" xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Text>CASE error_code OF&#xD;
	16#00000000: GetECErrMsg := 'No error';&#xD;
    16#04400000: GetECErrMsg := 'An error was detected in the hardware test at startup';&#xD;
    16#14400000: GetECErrMsg := 'The MAC address is incorrect';&#xD;
    16#44010000: GetECErrMsg := 'A fatal error was detected in the EtherCAT Master Function Module';&#xD;
    16#84200000: GetECErrMsg := 'A Link OFF state occurred';&#xD;
    16#842E0000: GetECErrMsg := 'The sent EtherCAT frame was not received';&#xD;
    16#24200000: GetECErrMsg := 'The same slave address is used for two nodes';&#xD;
    16#34400000: GetECErrMsg := 'There is an error in the network configuration information';&#xD;
    16#34410000: GetECErrMsg := 'Process data communications could not be performed with the specified communications cycle';&#xD;
    16#50010000: GetECErrMsg := 'The amount of data for the EtherCAT slave configuration, network-published info, or other data exceeds the value specified for the CPU Unit. You may not be able to perform online editing or other operations';&#xD;
    16#84210000: GetECErrMsg := 'The EtherCAT network configuration is incorrect';&#xD;
    16#84220000: GetECErrMsg := 'A slave that is in the network configuration information is not connected. Or, a slave that is not in the network configuration information is connected';&#xD;
    16#84230000: GetECErrMsg := 'Slave initialization failed';&#xD;
    16#84280000: GetECErrMsg := 'An error occurred in the slave application';&#xD;
    16#84290000: GetECErrMsg := 'Sending process data failed';&#xD;
    16#842B0000: GetECErrMsg := 'Process data reception timed out';&#xD;
    16#842C0000: GetECErrMsg := 'An error occurred in process data communications';&#xD;
    16#842F0000: GetECErrMsg := 'EtherCAT master could not perform process data communications normally. The Input Data Invalid state continued. Task period 10 ms or shorter: 100 ms. Longer than 10 ms: 10 periods of the task';&#xD;
    16#102F0000: GetECErrMsg := 'The backup operation for an EtherCAT slave ended in an error';&#xD;
    16#10300000: GetECErrMsg := 'The restore operation for an EtherCAT slave ended in an error';&#xD;
    16#64200000: GetECErrMsg := 'An emergency message was detected';&#xD;
    16#842D0000: GetECErrMsg := 'An error occurred in a message communications with the slave';&#xD;
    16#94400000: GetECErrMsg := 'A slave was disconnected for a disconnection command';&#xD;
    16#94410000: GetECErrMsg := 'A slave was reconnected for a reconnection command';&#xD;
    16#94430000: GetECErrMsg := 'A command was received to reset errors';&#xD;
    16#94440000: GetECErrMsg := 'The EtherCAT Slave was disabled';&#xD;
    16#94450000: GetECErrMsg := 'The EtherCAT Slave was enabled';&#xD;
    16#94500000: GetECErrMsg := 'EtherCAT diagnosis/statistics log is started';&#xD;
    16#94510000: GetECErrMsg := 'EtherCAT diagnosis/statistics log is ended';&#xD;
ELSE&#xD;
    GetECErrMsg := 'Unknown error code, check the documentation';&#xD;
END_CASE;&#xD;
</Text></StructuredTextModel>